export default data2 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "Which of the following is a fundamental principle of British life?",
        options: ["Communism", "Intolerance", "Individual liberty", "Inequity"],
        correct_option: "Individual liberty"
    },
    {
        id: "q2",
        question: "Wales has its own established church.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
    {
        id: "q3",
        question: "How is New Year’s Eve called in Scotland?",
        options: ["Vaisakhi", "Hannukah", "Diwali", "Hogmanay"],
        correct_option: "Hogmanay"
    },
    {
        id: "q4",
        question: "Why did Henry VIII establish the church of England?",
        options: ["To celebrate his wedding with Anne of Cleves", "To have control over religious people", "To establish a unique religion in England", "To divorce his first wife, Catherine of Aragon"],
        correct_option: "To divorce his first wife, Catherine of Aragon"
    },
    {
        id: "q5",
        question: "What is the name of the long war that English kings fought with France in the middle ages?",
        options: ["The Crimean War", "The First World War", "The Hundred Years War", "The Boer War"],
        correct_option: "The Hundred Years War"
    },
    {
        id: "q6",
        question: "Who was supported by clansmen from the Scottish highlands and raised and army in 1745?",
        options: ["Bonnie Prince Charlie", "Robert Burns", "Oliver Cromwell", "Kenneth MacAlpin"],
        correct_option: "Bonnie Prince Charlie"
    },
    {
        id: "q7",
        question: "It is compulsory for 16 and 17-year-olds to join the National Citizen Service programme.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
    {
        id: "q8",
        question: "What is the name of the tour guides that tell visitors stories about the Tower of London’s history?",
        options: ["Knights", "Chartists", "Suffragettes", "Beefeaters"],
        correct_option: "Beefeaters"
    },
    {
        id: "q9",
        question: "Where is Snowdonia located?",
        options: ["Scotland", "Wales", "England", "Northern Ireland"],
        correct_option: "Wales"
    },
    {
        id: "q10",
        question: "Who wrote Sherlock Holmes?",
        options: ["Evelyn Waugh", "Sir Kingsley Amis", "Graham Greene", "Sir Arthur Conan Doyle"],
        correct_option: "Sir Arthur Conan Doyle"
    },
    {
        id: "q11",
        question: "Which country was invaded by Germany in 1939?",
        options: ["Austria", "Italy", "Russia", "Poland"],
        correct_option: "Poland"
    },
    {
        id: "q12",
        question: "Who is the patron Saint of Wales?",
        options: ["St David", "St George", "St Patrick", "St Andrew"],
        correct_option: "St David"
    },
    {
        id: "q13",
        question: "What is the name of the area in London where famous theatres are located?",
        options: ["Soho", "Theatreland", "Westminster", "Hyde Park"],
        correct_option: "Theatreland"
    },
    {
        id: "q14",
        question: "When did the Black Death take place?",
        options: ["The Golden Age", "The Stone Age", "The Middle Ages", "The Iron Age"],
        correct_option: "The Middle Ages"
    },
    {
        id: "q15",
        question: "Who was the leader of the suffragettes, the group that campaigned for women’s rights to vote?",
        options: ["Queen Victoria", "Oliver Cromwell", "Florence Nightingale", "Emmeline Pankhurst"],
        correct_option: "Emmeline Pankhurst"
    },
    {
        id: "q16",
        question: "Cardiff is the capital city of which country?",
        options: ["Scotland", "Northern Ireland", "Ireland", "Wales"],
        correct_option: "Wales"
    },
    {
        id: "q17",
        question: "During the Great Depression in the 1930s which industry was badly affected?",
        options: ["Housing construction", "Shipbuilding", "Automobile", "Aviation"],
        correct_option: "Shipbuilding"
    },
    {
        id: "q18",
        question: "Who was the first man in the world to run 1 mile in under 4 minutes?",
        options: ["Sir Chris Hoy", "Sir Roger Bannister", "David Weir", "Mo Farah"],
        correct_option: "Sir Roger Bannister"
    },
    {
        id: "q19",
        question: "Which jubilee did Queen Elizabeth II celebrate in 2012?",
        options: ["Golden Jubilee", "Silver Jubilee", "Platinum Jubilee", "Diamond Jubilee"],
        correct_option: "Diamond Jubilee"
    },
    {
        id: "q20",
        question: "How often are the general elections held in the UK?",
        options: ["Every year", "Every 2 years", "Every 4 years", "Every 5 years"],
        correct_option: "Every 5 years"
    },
    {
        id: "q21",
        question: "Where is the Grand National horse racing event celebrated?",
        options: ["In London", "In Aintree", "In Bedford", "In Slough"],
        correct_option: "In Aintree"
    },
    {
        id: "q22",
        question: "What was Charles Chaplin famous for?",
        options: ["Special effects movies", "Horror movies", "Silent movies", "Murder-mystery movies"],
        correct_option: "Silent movies"
    },
    {
        id: "q23",
        question: "What was Boudicca, the queen of the Iceni in what is now eastern England, known for?",
        options: ["Her rebellion against the Vikings", "Her rebellion against the Romans", "Her rebellion against the Normans", "Her rebellion against the Anglo-Saxons"],
        correct_option: "Her rebellion against the Romans"
    },
    {
        id: "q24",
        question: "When was the hovercraft invented?",
        options: ["In the 1920s", "In the 1930s", "In the 1940s", "In the 1950s"],
        correct_option: "In the 1950s"
    }


]